rabble.ca 2007-12-14

# about us

### Privacy policy

_rabble.ca_ is committed to protecting the privacy of its members who visit and participate in the _rabble.ca_ Website and other users of the _rabble.ca_ Website. This Privacy Policy describes the practices of _rabble.ca_ in respect to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of information. This Privacy Policy can also be found online at __rabble.ca__. 

If you are a Member or User your use of the Site constitutes your consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, your sole remedy is to stop using the Site and/or return the legal plan to _rabble.ca_ within the thirty-day grace period.   
_rabble.ca_ may amend portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without your consent or authorization. _rabble.ca_ will notify you of any such changes, additions or deletions by posting notice of such changes on the Site and _rabble.ca_ encourages you to periodically check the Site to ensure that you are always informed of the then current terms of the Privacy Policy to which you are bound. Your continued use of the Site or of any services of _rabble.ca_ following notice of such changes constitutes your consent to the terms of the Privacy Policy as amended. 

Collection of Information From Prospective Plan Members   
All prospective Members will be required to complete an application form (each, an “Application Form”) and submit the completed Application Form to _rabble.ca_. The information which _rabble.ca_ will collect from each prospective Member as part of the Application Form will include, without limitation, the following (collectively, “Personal Information”): 

(a)

| name, e-mail address, and some demographic information; and   
---|---  
  
(b)

| other personal or business information that _rabble.ca_ may require.   
  
Collection of Additional Information   
From time to time _rabble.ca_ may request additional information from Members in connection with the provision of its services to Members. In addition, from time to time Members or other Users may elect to provide information to _rabble.ca_ through the Site or otherwise. All such information collected will constitute “Personal Information” and will be governed by the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

Collection of Traffic Data   
When you visit _rabble.ca_ , our systems collect basic information about your computer, including: IP address (your computer’s unique signature), operating system (e.g., Windows 95), browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape), Internet Service Provider (e.g., AOL). We also collect information about what you view on the site. This information reflects the user population as a whole and is used to help us better understand the _rabble.ca_ community. This information helps us identify popular features and content on our site. 

Use of Cookies to Collect Information from Users   
_rabble.ca_ monitors traffic on its Site using “cookies”. “Cookies” are small information packets that a website creates which are stored on the hard drive of a user’s computer by the user’s browser. _rabble.ca_ uses cookies to track and collect information relating to a User’s use of the Site, including, without limitation, the pages visited by Users, any special formation requested by Users and any other User preferences (collectively, “User Information”). If a User does not want _rabble.ca_ to collect such User Information, a User may reset his or her browser so that it does not accept cookies. Disabling cookies may limit a User’s ability to access some of the information or services available on the Site. 

Processing of Application Forms   
_rabble.ca_ uses the Personal Information it collects as part of the Application Form to process the applications of Members. In addition, _rabble.ca_ will use Personal Information and Plan Usage Information as required by it to provide continued service to its Members. _rabble.ca_ will also collect and store Personal Information collected from Members for back-up, archival and other record keeping purposes.   
Improvement of Site and User Customization   
_rabble.ca_ uses User Information collected in order to learn which areas of the Site are popular and which are not so that it can improve and update the Site and the information available on the Site. _rabble.ca_ also uses User Information to customize the delivery of information, services and advertisements to best meet a User’s preferences. 

E-Mail Notices   
After signing up online to receive an _rabble.ca_ e-mail notice, users will start receiving an e-mail notice and other occasional announcements from _rabble.ca_. In order to distribute our newsletters, we collect subscribers’ e-mail addresses. We do not share addresses with other companies or partners. Users can choose to unsubscribe from _rabble.ca_ e-mail list at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions found in the initial e-mail message sent to subscribers, visiting the newsletter sign-up page or sending e-mail to [business@rabble.ca](mailto:business@rabble.ca).  
_rabble.ca_ offers a service which allows our users to inform friends about an article they might be interested in reading. In order for this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses from the sender and for the recipient. We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive any communication from _rabble.ca_ as a result of having used this feature. 

babble   
_rabble.ca_ makes the babble discussion boards available to its Users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes publicly available and you should therefore exercise caution when disclosing Personal Information.   
You are responsible for the content of the messages that you post to babble. _rabble.ca_ does not assume any responsibility for the content that you or any other members post to babble.   
In order to post to babble, a user must become a member of rabble. Therefore the same policies apply. The information will be stored in a database and you will have the option to be automatically notified of messages related to your posts. You will not receive any additional communication from _rabble.ca_ as a result of having used this feature. However, all members may be contacted from time to time with general rabble communications.   
If you have any concerns about the message boards, send an e-mail to [babble@rabble.ca](mailto:babble@rabble.ca). 

Disclosure Required by Law   
_rabble.ca_ will not disclose Personal Information unless as required by law. Circumstances may arise in which _rabble.ca_ is compelled by law, court order, regulation, subpoena or other legal compulsion to disclose Personal Information to a third party or government authority. _rabble.ca_ will comply with all such legal obligations. In addition, _rabble.ca_ may disclose Personal Information if, in the good faith opinion of _rabble.ca_ , such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to: (a) conform to or comply with any law, regulation or court order; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of _rabble.ca_ or any of its suppliers or licensors, whether or not required to do so by law; or (c) protect the personal safety of Users or the public. _rabble.ca_ also reserves the right to disclose Personal Information to appropriate authorities at its discretion when it appears that activities which are illegal or in violation of any terms and conditions governing its services are taking place. 

_rabble.ca_ employs reasonable security safeguards in order to protect against the loss, misuse or interception by third parties of information under the control of _rabble.ca_. However, complete confidentiality and security is not yet possible over the Internet. _rabble.ca_ assumes no liability for any damages Users may suffer as a result of interception, alteration or misuse of information (including Personal Information) transmitted over the Internet. 

Any questions with respect to this Privacy Policy, or any request to access or change Personal Information, should be directed to [business@rabble.ca](mailto:business@rabble.ca). 

The Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the Province of Ontario and the federal laws of Canada applicable in Ontario. The User agrees to submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Ontario for any suit, action or other proceeding arising in connection with this Privacy Policy.
